- Hey, Josie.
- 嘿，乔茜。
A strawberry smoothie for me,
- 给我来杯草莓奶昔，
and for my little furry friend here,
- 还有我这位毛茸茸的小朋友，
a can of your finest meat.
- 来一罐你们最好的肉罐头。
- [barking]
- [汪汪]
- Make that two cans.
- 来两罐吧。
- Aw, look who got a new dog tag.
- 哦，看谁有了新狗牌。
So you guys finally agreed on a name?
- 所以你们终于决定名字了？
- Yep. My brothers just don't know it yet.
- 是的。我兄弟们还不知道呢。
- Won't they notice?
- 他们不会注意到吗？
- Please, they never notice anything.
- 拜托，他们从来不会注意到任何事情。
- I notice something.
- 我注意到了一些事情。
- I notice it too.
- 我也注意到了。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
Mom and Dad totally redid the cafe.
妈妈和爸爸完全重新装修了咖啡馆。
- We're talking about the dog tag.
- 我们在谈论狗牌。
It better say his name is, "Chip."
上面最好写着他的名字是，“Chip”。
- You mean, "Tiny Elvis."
- 你是说，“Tiny Elvis”。
- The tag should say, "Gary."
- 狗牌应该写着，“Gary”。
- Too late, fellas.
- 太晚了，伙计们。
The tag has spoken.
标签已经决定了。
His name is, "Squishy Paws."
他的名字是，“软软爪子”。
- No, it's not. [all arguing]
不，不是。
- Guys!
伙计们！
Guys! Guys!
伙计们！伙计们！
All your arguing is upsetting him.
你们这样争吵让他很不安。
Look, he's even doing his sad-tail thing.
看，他甚至在做他那悲伤尾巴的动作。
- Josie's right.
乔西说得对。
All this arguing is upsetting...
所有这些争吵都让他很不安……
Chip!
奇普！
[all arguing]
[所有人都在争论]
- So...
- 所以...
I hear we have a petty thief making his way around town.
我听说我们镇上有个小偷在四处作案。
Let me tell you, Mr. Boulder Bandit.
让我告诉你，巨石强盗先生。
You better think twice before you hit my store,
你最好在光顾我的店前再三考虑，
'cause I've got eyes...
因为我有眼睛...
in the sky.
在天上。
- Hey, Tom?
- 嘿，汤姆？
Were you expecting a T-shirt delivery?
你在等一批T恤送货吗？
- I'll ask the questions around here.
- 这里的问题由我来问。
And, yes. Yes, I was.
是的，没错，我确实在期待一件T恤的送达。
Does it look a little something like this?
它是不是看起来有点像这样？
- Uh, no, they look a little more like this.
- 呃，不，它们看起来更像是这样。
- What? No, no! I sent them the picture
- 什么？不，不！我给他们发了穿着T恤的照片作为例子。
of me wearing the T-shirt as an example.
他们不应该把我印在T恤上。
They weren't supposed to put me on the shirt.
- 嗯，我想你可以把它们退回去。
- Well, I guess you could just return them.
- [清嗓子] 哇，哇。
- [clears throat] Hoo, wow.
- 等等，等等，等等，等等。
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
你确实确认了他们有退货政策
You did make sure they had a return policy
在你订购6000件之前，对吧？
before you ordered 6,000, right?
在你订购6,000件之前，你确实确认了他们有退货政策，对吧？
- I told you...
- 我告诉过你...
I'll ask the questions around here.
这里的问题应该由我来问。
Now, if you'll excuse me...
现在，如果你不介意的话...
I-I'm going to go call and ask that question.
我-我要去打电话问那个问题。
[all arguing]
[所有人都在争论]
- [barks]
- [吠叫]
[barking]
[吠叫]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
Get him off!
把他弄走！
把他弄下来！
- He caught the Boulder Bandit.
他抓住了巨石强盗。
Squishy Paws is a hero!
软爪是英雄！
- Chip's a hero!
奇普是英雄！
- Good job, Tiny Elvis.
干得好，小埃尔维斯。
- The hero is Gary!
英雄是加里！
[all cheering]
大家都在欢呼
- Well, looks like someone's having a...
嗯，看起来某人正在经历一个...
"ruff" day.
糟糕的一天。
[screaming]
尖叫声
- [barking] - Ah! Ah!
（狗叫声） 啊！啊！
[upbeat music]
（欢快音乐）
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
（吹口哨旋律）
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
（有节奏的拍手） ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
（吹口哨旋律）
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- Squishy, before you watch yourself on the news, look!
斯奎西，在你看到自己在新闻上之前，看！
Someone sent you a dozen long-stemmed "boneses."
有人送了你一打长茎的“骨头”。
- He sure doesn't have sad tail now.
他现在肯定没有悲伤的尾巴了。
Eat up, little hero.
吃吧，小英雄。
- I can't believe the Harpers are going to be on TV.
我真不敢相信哈珀一家会上电视。
- And I can't believe I'm here with a celebrity.
而我真不敢相信我和一位名人在一起。
- I'm just a boy from Boulder, Liv.
我只是来自博尔德的一个男孩，丽芙。
- Oh, I just want to snuggle him.
哦，我只想抱抱他。
- Ladies, ladies,
女士们，女士们，
tonight was supposed to be about the dog.
今晚本应该是关于狗狗的。
- Anne, our T-shirt problems are solved.
安妮，我们的T恤问题解决了。
- Oh, they took them back?
哦，他们收回去了？
- Better-- I went to a different shop
更好的是——我去了一家不同的店
and made these.
然后做了这些。
What do you have to say now, Anne?
你现在有什么要说的，安妮？
- Oh, Tom.
哦，汤姆。
- [gasps] It's coming on!
（喘气）开始了！
- Oh!
哦！
- Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News,
- 维罗妮卡·米勒，Channel 6新闻，
moments after the Boulder Bandit was apprehended.
在巨石强盗被捕后的片刻。
But the real story is, by whom.
但真正的故事是，由谁捕获的。
Would you believe this underdog?
你相信这个不被看好的人吗？
- [barks] - Oh.
- [吠叫] - 哦。
[all clapping]
（众人鼓掌）
- I know him! Aw, I know him!
- 我认识他！哦，我认识他！
- But the story doesn't end there.
- 但故事并没有就此结束。
Turns out the owners of this hero dog
原来这位英雄狗的主人
are none other than the Harper quadruplets.
正是哈珀四胞胎。
- I know them! I know them!
我认识他们！我认识他们！
- Remember that quad-orable little foursome?
记得那四个可爱的小家伙吗？
- Aww.
啊。
- They were the pride of Boulder--
他们是博尔德的骄傲——
so sweet and cuddly.
那么甜美和可爱。
How did it go so horribly wrong?
怎么会变得如此糟糕？
- Nicky,
尼基，
Ricky,
里基，
Dicky,
迪基，
and Dawn.
和道恩。
- What's happening?
发生什么事了？
- Watch what happened when I asked them a simple question.
看看当我问他们一个简单问题时发生了什么。
It was nothing short of a...
这简直是一场...
quad-tastrophe.
四重灾难。
So tell us, what is the name of this courageous dog?
那么告诉我们，这只勇敢的狗叫什么名字？
- It's Squishy Paws!
是Squishy Paws！
- No, Veronica, it's Chip.
不，Veronica，它叫Chip。
- Don't listen to them. It's Tiny Elvis.
别听他们的。它是Tiny Elvis。
- The dog is a Gary.
这只狗叫Gary。
[all arguing]
[所有人争吵]
- One dog, four names.
一只狗，四个名字。
The Harper kids have gone from quad-orable...
哈珀家的孩子们已经从四倍的可爱...
[echoing] to quad-horrible.
变成了四倍的糟糕。
But the one who suffers most here
但在这里最受苦的那个
shall remain...
将保持...
nameless.
无名。
- She made us look like animals.
她让我们看起来像动物。
- Who can't take care of animals.
连动物都照顾不好。
- Come on, we didn't look that bad.
拜托，我们看起来没那么糟。
Right, guys?
对吧，伙计们？
- Uh, I've got to go return a library book.
- 呃，我得去还一本图书馆的书。
- I have to buy envelopes.
- 我得去买信封。
- Oh, I'm just uncomfortable.
- 哦，我只是觉得不舒服。
- Relax, it's only a few friends.
- 放松，只是几个朋友而已。
[all murmuring disapprovingly]
[大家都低声表示不满]
Relax, it's only a store full of customers.
放松，只是满店的顾客。
- It's not just them. You've gone viral.
- 不只是他们。你已经火了。
Everyone's calling you "The Horrible Harpers."
大家都叫你们“可怕的哈珀一家”。
- Is that a lot of hits?
- 那点击量很多吗？
18 comma 0, 0, 0, comma, 0, 0--
18,000,000,000,000,000,000--
- Yes, Dicky, it's a lot.
是的，迪基，很多。
- Maybe Dad should be selling "Horrible Harper" T-shirts.
也许爸爸应该卖‘可怕哈珀’T恤。
- Step right up, folks!
大家快来！
Get your "hero dog" T-shirts.
来买‘英雄狗’T恤。
[chuckles] Be the first person on your block to buy one.
（轻笑）成为你街区第一个买的人。
Be the first person at your school to buy one.
成为你学校第一个买的人。
- Or just be the first person to buy one.
或者就成为第一个买的人。
- Why aren't they buying them?
他们为什么不买？
- Because we're the horrible parents
因为我们是有可怕孩子的父母
of The Horrible Harpers.
来自可怕哈珀家。
- We're the horrible kids of the horrible parents
- 我们是那些可怕父母的可怕孩子
of The Horrible Harpers.
可怕的哈珀一家
- You could've just said we're The Horrible Harpers.
- 你其实可以直接说我们是可怕的哈珀一家
- And we could've just called the dog Tiny Elvis!
- 而我们本可以简单地给狗取名叫小埃尔维斯！
- Gary! - Chip!
- 加里！ - 奇普！
- Hold on!
- 等等！
If a news story got us into this,
如果一个新闻故事把我们卷入这一切，
maybe a different one could get us out.
也许另一个不同的故事能让我们脱身。
"Quaddle" up.
“准备”好了。
Actually, that was the plan, sorry for the false "quaddle."
实际上，那是计划，抱歉误导你“准备”了。
- Okay, this better be good.
好吧，这最好是有价值的。
What's the big juicy story you called me down here for?
你叫我来这里，有什么大新闻？
- We want you to do another segment on us
我们希望你再为我们做一个专题
so we can be The Quad-orable Harpers again.
这样我们就能再次成为可爱的哈珀一家了。
- We're not bad dog owners.
我们不是坏主人。
- Yeah, we adopted him from the pound.
是的，我们是从收容所领养他的。
That's good, right?
那很好，对吧？
- Wow.
哇。
I just took an open-eyed nap.
我刚刚打了个睁眼盹。
Sorry, kids, but that's not newsworthy.
抱歉，孩子们，但这不是新闻。
That's snooze-worthy.
那真是值得打个盹的事。
Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News.
我是 Veronica Miller，6 频道新闻。
- Wait.
等等。
We shouldn't be punished just because we couldn't decide
我们不能因为无法在 Chip、Gary、Squishy Paws 和 Tiny Elvis 之间做出决定而受罚。
between Chip, Gary, Squishy Paws, and Tiny Elvis.
他的名字不是那些可笑的东西之一。
- His name is none of those ridiculous things.
他的名字是 Lord Timothy。
It's Lord Timothy.
大家：“Lord Timothy”？
All: "Lord Timothy"?
你是谁？
- Who are you?
我是这只狗的合法主人，
- I am the dog's rightful owner,
我来把他从 The Horrible Harpers 带回去。
and I've come to retrieve him
并且我来接他
from The Horrible Harpers.
从可怕的哈珀家。
- Now, that's newsworthy.
现在，这可是新闻。
Okay.
好的。
Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News.
维罗妮卡·米勒，第六频道新闻。
Hero dog update.
英雄狗的最新消息。
Someone has just stepped forward
刚刚有人站出来
claiming to be his rightful owner.
声称是他的合法主人。
Your name?
你的名字？
- Eleanor Dumont.
埃莉诺·杜蒙特。
Lord Timothy disappeared after a fire
蒂莫西勋爵在一场火灾后失踪了，
at my country home during the high lake season.
那场火灾发生在我乡间别墅的高湖季节。
So you can imagine my surprise
所以你可以想象当我看到他在你们的新闻节目中时的惊讶。
when I saw him on your news program.
- 她在撒谎！ - [惊呼]
- She's lying! - [gasps]
- 是的，她只是想要我们的英雄狗。
- Yeah, she just wants our hero dog.
- 嘿，大家冷静下来。我们会处理这件事。
- Hey, everybody calm down. We'll handle this.
- 对不起，女士，但你不能就这样带着我们孩子的狗离开这里。
- I'm sorry, ma'am, but you can't just walk out of here
但你可以带着他可爱的脸庞离开这里
with our kids' dog.
在这件帅气的T恤上！
But you can walk out of here with his adorable face
当然，我已经来了
on this handsome T-shirt!
在这件帅气的T恤上！
- Naturally, I have come
当然，我带来了
with the appropriate documentation.
相应的文件。
- Paperwork, really?
文件，真的吗？
Anyone can fake paperwork.
任何人都可以伪造文件。
- Yeah.
是的。
I fake paperwork all the time.
我经常伪造文件。
I'm not an actual real estate agent.
我不是真正的房地产经纪人。
I just use my fake card to impress the ladies.
我只是用我的假名片来吸引女士们。
- You spelled "real" and "estate" incorrectly.
你把“real”和“estate”拼错了。
- But I spelled my number right.
- 但我号码拼对了。
Call me.
打给我。
- If you're really his owner,
- 如果你真是他的主人，
then what does the birthmark on his stomach look like?
那他肚子上的胎记是什么样的？
- The Mona Lisa.
- 蒙娜丽莎。
- She's right.
- 她说得对。
- Of course I'm right.
- 当然是我对。
- Kids, I'm sorry, but he does seem to be her dog.
- 孩子们，抱歉，但他似乎确实是她的狗。
- Of course he's my dog.
- 他当然是我的狗。
- Lord Timothy! Andiamo!
- 蒂莫西大人！走吧！
- He's fluent in Italian.
他意大利语说得很流利。
Oh, I can't thank you children enough.
哦，我真不知道该怎么感谢你们这些孩子。
If it hadn't been for your bickering,
如果不是因为你们的争吵，
I never would have seen Lord Timothy on the news,
我永远不会在新闻上看到Lord Timothy，
and he wouldn't be going home with me right now.
他现在也不会和我一起回家。
Ta.
谢谢。
- Well, there you have it.
好吧，就是这样。
Guess every dog does have his day.
看来每只狗都有他的好日子。
- [laughs] That was good.
（笑）那真不错。
- Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News.
Veronica Miller，第6频道新闻。
Huh, turned out to be big and juicy after all.
哈，结果还是又大又多汁。
Ta.
Ta。
- Now I know what sad tail feels like.
——现在我知道尾巴悲伤是什么感觉了。
- I miss petting Chip.
——我想念抚摸奇普。
- I miss playing with Tiny Elvis.
——我想念和小泰尼·埃尔维斯玩耍。
- [whimpering]
——[呜咽声]
- Guys! Help!
——伙计们！帮帮忙！
Does--does any of this match?
这些——这些有匹配的吗？
Squishy used to help me get dressed.
斯奎西以前帮我穿衣服。
One bark meant, "You are rocking that."
一声吠叫意味着，“你穿得很棒。”
two meant, "Total fashion disaster."
两声意味着，“完全的时尚灾难。”
- In that case, woof, woof.
- 那样的话，汪汪。
- I knew it.
- 我就知道。
I'm lost without him.
没有他我迷失了。
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，伙计们。
Tough morning?
早上很难熬吗？
- We really miss the dog, Dad.
- 我们真的很想念那只狗，爸爸。
- Yeah, it's not the same without him.
- 是的，没有他不一样。
- I wish we hadn't fought so much.
- 我希望我们没那么多争吵。
- Look, I know this is hard, but you got to figure out a way to put the dog out of your mind.
- 听着，我知道这很难，但你必须想办法把狗从你心中排除。
Now, I'm not going to hound you, but-- - "Hound"? Too soon, Dad.
- Sorry, kiddo. It just slipped out.
I'm gonna fetch you up some "barkfast."
Breakfast.
It's the leash I can do. Wow!
What is wrong with me?
Who wants beagles? Bagels!
Doggone it. Ah!
I'm just going to walk out with my tail between my legs.
Stop it! "Fleas" forgive me!
I said "fleas"!
我说的是“跳蚤”！
Bad Tom! Bad Tom!
坏汤姆！坏汤姆！
- Oh, hey. Care to explain our new bath towels, Tom?
- 哦，嘿。介意解释一下我们的新浴巾，汤姆吗？
- Oh, well, I figured why take a bath on the shirts when we can take a bath with the shirts.
- 哦，好吧，我想既然可以在衬衫上洗澡，为什么还要用浴巾呢。
See where you see failure, I see opportunity.
在你看到失败的地方，我看到了机会。
- Well, at least it wasn't a bedspread or curtains.
- 嗯，至少不是床单或窗帘。
Ugh. Bad Tom. Bad Tom.
呃。坏汤姆。坏汤姆。
- Maybe it will help take our minds off the dog
- 也许看电视能让我们暂时不去想那只狗。
if we watch TV.
如果我们看电视的话。
- Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News.
- 维罗妮卡·米勒，6频道新闻。
Hero dog update.
英雄狗狗最新消息。
- Not cool, TV.
电视真扫兴。
- At least we get to see him again.
至少我们又能看到他了。
- We're here at the Dumont Mansion
我们现在在杜蒙特庄园，
checking in with Lord Timothy
正在与蒂莫西勋爵交谈，
after his rescue from The Horrible Harpers.
他在被可怕的哈珀家族救出后。
And rest assured, our hero dog is now living
请放心，我们的英雄狗狗现在正过着
the life of luxury he so richly deserves.
他应得的那种奢华生活。
- Hey, look, he has his sad tail.
嘿，看，他的尾巴还是那么悲伤。
- And there.
就在那儿。
- Maybe he misses us as much as we miss him.
也许他像我们想念他一样想念我们。
- We need to visit him and try to cheer him up.
我们需要去看看他，试着让他开心起来。
- She lives by the golf course in Boulderly Hills.
她住在Boulderly Hills的高尔夫球场附近。
We can walk there.
我们可以步行去那里。
- Let's go.
走吧。
- Boulderly Hills is pretty fancy.
Boulderly Hills相当高档。
You sure you want to go out looking all "woof, woof"?
你确定要这样‘汪汪’地出去吗？
- Just let's go.
我们走吧。
[doorbell rings]
（门铃响）
- Oh.
哦。
Well, if it isn't Nicky, Ricky, Dicky,
哎呀，这不是Nicky、Ricky、Dicky，
and the one that doesn't rhyme.
还有那个不押韵的。
- Hi. We're sorry to bother you.
- 嗨。很抱歉打扰你们。
We were wondering if we could visit Lord Timothy?
我们想知道是否可以拜访Timothy大人？
- Very well.
- 很好。
Walk this way.
这边请。
Wait in here while I inform Ms. Dumont of your visit.
在这里稍等，我去通知Dumont女士你们的来访。
- This place is awesome.
- 这个地方真棒。
At least Tiny Elvis is living large.
至少Tiny Elvis过得挺滋润的。
- Wow. Guess she really likes dogs.
- 哇。看来她真的很喜欢狗。
- Guys?
伙计们？
Why would Ms. Dumont have a dog fur on the wall?
杜蒙特女士为什么会在墙上挂狗毛？
- And a dog skeleton?
还有狗的骨架？
- And a doggie cookbook?
还有狗狗食谱？
- Aah!
啊！
The horror!
太可怕了！
Ah, there he is.
啊，他在这儿。
- Ms. Dumont is a real-life Cruella de Vil.
杜蒙特女士简直就是现实版的库伊拉。
- She's gonna turn Chip into a fur coat.
她要把奇普变成一件毛皮大衣。
- And then she's going to serve Gary for dinner.
然后她还要把加里当晚餐。
- Someone's coming. Act normal.
有人来了，表现正常。
- Presenting Lord Timothy, fresh from the bath.
呈上刚沐浴完的提摩西勋爵。
- Squishy Paws. - Chip.
软爪。- 奇普。
- Tiny Elvis. - Gary.
小猫王。- 盖瑞。
- Ms. Dumont is granting you five minutes alone.
杜蒙女士给你们五分钟独处时间。
- [barking]
[吠叫]
- I know, I'm a total fashion disaster.
我知道，我是个彻底的时尚灾难。
"Quaddle" up! - Wait.
“围起来”！- 等等。
Is the a real "quaddle"?
这是真的“围起来”吗？
- Because "quaddle" me once... - Just get in here.
因为“围起来”我一次...- 快进来吧。
We need to sneak Squishy Paws out of here
我们需要偷偷把'软爪'带出这里
before he ends up on a wall.
免得他最后被挂在墙上。
- Or on a menu.
- 或者被端上菜单。
- Where do you think you're going with Lord Timothy?
- 你以为你要带蒂莫西大人去哪儿？
All: Aah!
所有人：啊！
- She's a butcher!
- 她是个屠夫！
- Stop them!
- 拦住他们！
All: Aah!
所有人：啊！
- He's a butler!
- 他是个管家！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
All: Aah!
大家：啊！
♪ ♪
- Study!
学习！
- We need to find a way out of here.
我们需要找到离开这里的方法。
- Squishy, do you know a way?
Squishy，你知道有什么办法吗？
- [barks] - Sweet, Tiny Elvis.
汪汪 - 甜心，小埃尔维斯。
- Come on, come on. Go, go, go, go.
快点，快点。走，走，走，走。
- Whoa. - Yes!
- 哇。 - 是的！
We did it. We saved him.
我们做到了。我们救了他。
All: Aah!
所有人: 啊！
- How did she get here?
- 她是怎么到这里来的？
- I bet the butler did it!
- 我打赌是管家干的！
- I did. I drove her here.
- 是我。我开车带她来的。
- What were you kids thinking?
- 你们这些孩子当时在想什么？
You can't just take her dog.
你们不能就这样带走她的狗。
- She was going to turn Squishy Paws into a fur coat.
- 她打算把Squishy Paws做成一件毛皮大衣。
- Oh, come on, he's barely big enough for a vest.
- 哦，拜托，他连一件背心都做不了。
Earmuffs, maybe. - It's true, Dad!
可能是耳罩吧。- 是真的，爸爸！
She has dog furs and dog skeletons at her house!
她家里有狗毛和狗骨架！
- And a dog cookbook!
- 还有一本狗肉食谱！
She was gonna make mutt-loaf out of Gary.
她打算用Gary做狗肉饼。
- And she was dressed like a butcher.
- 而且她打扮得像个屠夫。
- Oh. I was only dressed that way
- 哦。我那样打扮只是因为我在给Lord Timothy洗澡。
because I was bathing Lord Timothy.
- 那你的小狗狗末日密室呢？
- Then what about your little doggy chamber of doom?
- 我能理解你们为什么会这么想。
- I can see why you might think these things.
但我绝不会伤害一只狗。
But I would never hurt a dog.
我是一名犬类历史学家。
I am a canine historian.
And the things that you saw were ancient artifacts--
而你所看到的那些东西是古代文物——
wolf pelts worn by hunters,
猎人穿的狼皮，
the skeleton of an extinct species,
一种已灭绝物种的骨骼，
and a cookbook of recipes
以及一本为狗制作的食谱，
made for dogs,
不是用狗肉做的。
not out of dogs.
- I think you kids owe Ms. Dumont an apology.
我想你们这些孩子应该向杜蒙特女士道歉。
- Do we? Do we?
我们真的需要吗？真的需要吗？
- Pretty sure we do, Dicky.
非常确定我们需要，迪基。
- Oh. Then sorry, Ms. Dumont.
哦。那对不起，杜蒙女士。
- Yeah, we're really sorry.
是的，我们真的很抱歉。
- It's all right.
没关系。
I know that you were just looking out
我知道你们都是为了提摩西勋爵的福祉着想。
for Lord Timothy's welfare.
尽管让我很痛苦，但现在是时候说再见了。
And as much as it pains me, it's time to say good-bye.
我想这就是分别的时候了，软爪。
- Guess this is it, Squishy Paws.
再见了，奇普。- 我会想念你的，加里。
- Good-bye, Chip. - I'm gonna miss you, Gary.
击掌告别，小猫王。
- High paw, Tiny Elvis.
我是说我该说再见了。
- I meant it's time for me to say good-bye.
什么？
All: What?
大家：什么？
- When I first saw the news report,
- 当我第一次看到新闻报道时，
I thought that you didn't care about him.
我以为你不在乎他。
But when you thought that he was in danger
但当你认为他有危险
and you risked so much to save him,
并且你冒了那么大的风险去救他，
well, now I know that I was wrong.
好吧，现在我知道我错了。
And judging from his happy tail,
而且从他快乐的尾巴来看，
he cares about you too.
他也很在乎你。
This is his new home now.
这是他现在的新家。
- Yes. - Thank you so much, Ms. Dumont!
- 是的。 - 非常感谢，杜蒙特女士！
- Thank you! - Thank you so much!
- 谢谢您！- 非常感谢您，杜蒙特女士！
- Yes! - Thank you, Ms. Dumont.
- 是的！- 谢谢您，杜蒙特女士。
- Oh, you're so welcome.
- 哦，不用客气。
- I'm really sorry I poked holes in your painting.
- 我真的很抱歉在您的画上戳了洞。
- What?
- 什么？
- Nothing.
- 没事。
- We promise to give this little guy a good home.
- 我们保证会给这个小家伙一个温馨的家。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Maybe we should start by finally agreeing on his name.
- 也许我们应该从最终确定他的名字开始。
- And no fighting this time.
- 这次不准吵架了。
- How are we gonna do that?
- 我们该怎么做呢？
- Veronica Miller, Channel 6 News,
- 维罗妮卡·米勒，第六频道新闻，
reporting live on the final chapter
现场报道我们英雄狗故事的最终章。
in our hero dog story.
昨天那四个爱争执的四胞胎无法决定名字。
Yesterday the quibbling quads couldn't decide on a name.
但今天他们达成了一个...
But today they came to a...
四胞胎的承诺。
Quad-promise.
他们会让狗自己决定！
They will let the dog decide!
五个碗，五个名字，
Five bowls, five names,
一个决定。
one decision.
好了，小家伙。去选你的名字吧！
- Okay, buddy.
好的，伙计。
Go pick your name!
去选你的名字吧！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Ladies and gentlemen, presenting...
女士们先生们，有请...
All: Squishy Paws!
所有人：软爪！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- [barks]
[吠叫]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
[欢快的旋律]
- ♪
♪